http://www.generaltool.com/about-mi/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - Motion
Feedback English
English
Français
Español Your accountRegisterSign InSIGN IN USERNAME OR EMAIL PASSWORDRemember MeSign InForgot your username or password?
All Products AbrasivesAdhesives, Sealants & TapeBearingsChemicals, Lubricants & EquipmentCutting ToolsElectricalFacility MaintenanceHand & Power ToolsHose & FittingsHydraulicsJanitorialLinear MotionMaterial HandlingMechanical Power TransmissionPneumaticsProcess Pumps & EquipmentSafetySeals, Gaskets & AccessoriesAbrasivesAdhesives, Sealants & TapeBearingsChemicals, Lubricants & EquipmentCutting ToolsElectricalFacility MaintenanceHand & Power ToolsHose & FittingsHydraulicsJanitorialLinear MotionMaterial HandlingMechanical Power TransmissionPneumaticsProcess Pumps & EquipmentSafetySeals, Gaskets & Accessories Search by product name or part number
SEARCH IN All Motion Industries
Abrasives
Adhesives, Sealants & Tape
Bearings
Chemicals, Lubricants & Equipment
Cutting Tools
Electrical
Facility Maintenance
Seals, Gaskets & Accessories
Searching in All Motion IndustriesPRODUCTSLocationsKnowledge HubPrintEffective Date 12/2019Motion Industries Privacy Notice In this Privacy Notice (“Notice”), Motion Industries (also referred to as “Motion,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) describes the types of personal information we may collect from you in connection with your interaction with us, including when you visit our branches, websites, mobile application, online services or otherwise interact with us (the “Services”) that display this notice. These Services include services available through our branches, motionindustries.com, social media websites, or other online products, services, content we offer. 1.PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTa.Personal information We Collect Directly from You We collect personal information from you when you use our Services and interact with us. The information we collect includes: your name, address, phone number, company, email address, and other information you choose to provide us, including when you register with our Services. We may also collect information relating to: Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.Your responses to surveys, such as those that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.Details of transactions you carry out through our Services. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Services. Financial transactions are carried our through a secure server. We do not store credit card information on our servers or systems. Contact information from the registration form, order forms, contest forms, and other sources.b.Personal information We Collect Automatically We collect information automatically when you interact with our Services online or via a mobile application. For example, we may use cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies to collect information about you as you use our Services. Examples of this type of information include the dates and times of your use of the Services, your IP (Internet Protocol) address, your browser type, your operating system, device identifiers, and the webpages or content to or from which you navigate.
Third parties may use cookies or similar technologies on our Services. For example, these technologies may be used to provide content, advertisements, and other services. We do not control third parties who may use these technologies to collect personal information about you, including information about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you use our Services. c.Personal Information We Collect From Third Parties We also collect information about you from third parties, such as marketing agencies and analytics and information providers. We may combine information we collect about you with information from third parties. 2.HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION We use the information we gather to provide services to you and to respond to your inquiries. This includes:
Providing services, including to: Register, create, and maintain your account;Allow you to purchase products online;Communicate with you regarding your account or any Services you use;Improve the convenience and functionality if our website;Evaluate applications. Manage our business and protect ourselves, you, other persons, and the Services.Provide a personalized experience and implement your preferences.Better understand our customers and how they use and interact with the Services.Market to you and provide personalized services, offers, and promotions on our websites and third-party websites.Comply with our policies and obligations, including, but not limited to, disclosures and responses in response to any requests from law enforcement authorities and/or regulators in accordance with any applicable law, rule, regulation, judicial or governmental order, regulatory authority of competent jurisdiction, discovery request, advice of counsel or similar legal process.Resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems.Provide customer service to you or otherwise communicate with you. We may also process your personal information to fulfill the purposes for which you provide it, or with your consent. 3.HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION We may disclose the information we gather with our affiliates and third parties. For example, we may share information with: Service providers and/or data processors: We may share personal information with third-party service providers that perform services and functions at our direction and on our behalf (including your local Motion branches). These third-party service providers may, for example, provide you with Services, assist in processing transactions, or provide customer support. Financial institutions and other companies involved in helping carry out the transactions in which you engage. Other third-parties for our business purposes or as permitted or required by law, including:
To comply with any legal, regulatory or contractual obligation, or with any legal or regulatory process (such as a valid court order or subpoena) or advice of counsel; To third parties to market our or their products or services to you;To establish, exercise, or defend legal claims or our policies; If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud prevention and credit risk reduction; or
In connection with the purchase, sale, merger, consolidation or transfer of all or part of our business.
We may also disclose data to fulfill the purposes for which you provide it, or with your consent. 4.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE We reserve the right to modify this Notice from time to time and we will notify you of changes to this Notice by revising this notice and updating the Effective Date above. If we make any material changes to this Notice we will notify you by posting a notice on our website OR emailing you OR providing appropriate notice. 5.YOUR CHOICES If you wish to stop receiving marketing communications, you can opt out by emailing us at HelpDesk@Motion-ind.com. We may continue to send you non-marketing messages, such as messages relating to your transactions with us.
As of the Effective Date listed above, there is no commonly accepted response for Do Not Track signals initiated by browsers. Therefore, we do not respond to such signals or to other mechanisms that provide the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information regarding your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services.
If you are a registered user of the Services, you may access your personal account information online and make changes by logging into your account.
You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited. You may control how your browser accepts cookies; please see our cookie policy for more information. 6.SECURITY We have implemented administrative, physical and technical safeguards designed to protect your personal information. Still, we cannot guarantee the security or confidentiality of information you transmit to us or receive from us. 7.CALIFORNIA PRIVACY PRACTICES AND YOUR CALIFORNIA RIGHTS If you are a California resident, click here for more information about our privacy practices and your rights under California law. 8.CONTACT US We take your privacy concerns seriously. If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or if you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Notice with respect to your personal information, you may write to HelpDesk@Motion-Ind.com. Customer ServiceShop & OrderTrack OrdersRequest a QuoteFind a LocationContact UsResourcesKnowledge HubMi Learning and DevelopmentSupplier inMotionSite MapCompany InformationAbout UsCareersPress ReleasesInvestor Relations1-800-526-9328Mon - Fri 7 a.m. to 5 p.m.Sat - Sun Closed Follow UsCustomer ServiceShop & OrderTrack OrdersRequest a QuoteFind a LocationContact UsResourcesKnowledge HubMi Learning and DevelopmentSupplier inMotionSite MapCompany InformationAbout UsCareersPress ReleasesCorporate SustainabilityCommunity RelationsInvestor RelationsEvents1-800-526-9328Mon - Fri 7 a.m. to 5 p.m.Sat - Sun Closed 1-800-526-9328Follow UsFollow Us1-800-526-9328Copyright © 2001 - 2020 Motion Industries, Inc. - All Rights Reserved.  Legal Disclaimer,  Privacy Policy,  Terms and Conditions,  Provide FeedbackMotion Industries 1605 Alton Rd.Birmingham, AL 35210, USA (205) 956-1122, 1-800-526-9328Motion Industries 1605 Alton Rd. Birmingham, AL 35210, USA (205) 956-1122, 1-800-526-9328Legal DisclaimerPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsProvide Feedbackv20.10.08-72
